wordstemplates.org 2018-04-09

# Privacy Policy | Free Word Templates

Following is the drafted privacy policy of this website. By visiting this website, I assume that you have gone through the contents of this privacy policy. Therefore, it is critical to view and understand this policy.

**Purpose**

I has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its obligation toward the privacy and protection of your information. It is notable that I gather and, in some instances, disclose information pertaining to you in routine operations. To save guard your privacy, I present this policy clearly depicting our stance and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Third Party Advertisement**

I may use third party advertisement programs for the purpose to meet the cost of this website; that include the payments to its employees, other associates, technical staff, hosting services and any other cost that I feel appropriate. I would like to inform you that some of these advertisers  **(like Google, Info links & Chitika)** may use technologies such to send cookies and web beacons when their ads display on this site. The purpose behind this activity is to gather the information of user so most appropriate ad can be displayed. This information may include your IP address, your ISP, the browser, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed or not.

Furthermore, this site holds the right to use DART cookies for ad serving through advertisers like Google’s DoubleClick. Google’s DoubleClick is shows ads which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising. DART advertising programs are using “Interest Bases Targeting” technique which shows only your interest related ads. Base on your browser history data, these ads displayed will be targeted. We believe in your privacy, therefore inform you that DART is base on  **“Non personally identifiable information”  **policy. Remember that it  **does NOT**  track your personal information, like your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. However, you have the power to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies through your browser’s settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security or other security programs. However, this can cause problem you while visiting different sites as well as the inability to log in to services and logging into forums or accounts.

**Email Privacy**

Users of this website are informed that we do not provide email address to any party for any reason. Your email address is saved with us and thus you don’t need to worry about. We do not sell or inform email addresses of our users or those who have subscribed for new posts.

**General Terms and Conditions**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Agreement of this website.

If you have any query or question regarding the privacy policy, I hereby, advice you to contact us and don’t use this site till than.
